I'm not carrying you back.
I'm not going back.
You can pack my bags and bring them here.
I'm staying at Teacher Fu's.
Mmm.
This is Teacher Feng.
These are the two college
students who came to volunteer here.
Here's to you.
Teacher Fu, a toast to you.
Hello, Chairman Ye.
You're just in time.
Let me introduce you.
This is Chairman Ye, the
head of our Tea Association.
A pleasure to meet you. Hello.
Let's drink together.
Enjoy your meal.
Come on, another one. Stand up. Come on.
My brother says he's not
going back to your place.
He wants me to bring his luggage over.
I know.
"A Winter Sun Wakes the Wind in Spring Hills' Dream"
(Episode 4: Life Path)
Sister Lan.
Was I a bit too much?
When you're drunk, yes.
But when I don't get a response,
I tend to act like this.
Another Shi Yuhao.
It's different.
He doesn't run away.
He just doesn't need me.
Liking someone isn't about
making them need you.
Let liking just be liking.
Don't turn it into a need.
[Let liking just be liking.]
[Love "You" [Honorific]]
What happened between
you and my brother last night?
He asked me if I like men.
And the truth is?
It's not important.
Answering like that would
definitely trigger my brother.
My brother hates vague answers.
It really isn't important.
It's like these tea plants.
The experts come,
measure how many meters
the roots go into the ground,
collect a bunch of data,
but in the end, isn't it all judged
by whether the tea tastes good?
Be practical.
A kilogram, a ton,
no matter how much tea, it
all has to be picked leaf by leaf.
A lot of things that are set in stone
can only be changed one step at a time.
Are you serious?
I'm selling tea tomorrow.
I need to know how tea
gets from the tree to the cup.
Didn't you get a taste of it yesterday?
Experiencing it and doing
it are two different things.
I want to make a batch of
my own tea from start to finish.
I'm heading to the fields.
After you eat, I'll take you to work.
Tomorrow is the Dragon-Elephant Festival.
So eat more meat tonight.
You really can't eat meat during
the Dragon-Elephant Festival?
And you can't 'ku-ku-ku'.
What does that mean?
Ask him, he doesn't know anything.
Come on, another one.
Come on, come on.
Hey.
We're wrapping up filming soon.
Do you have classes when
you go back to school?
No, I have to rehearse
for the graduation play.
You'll probably have to help
with promoting our show, right?
Mmm-hmm.
Our company's post-production is very fast.
It can be released in two months.
The promotion will probably start
before those two months are up.
Oh.
I think we could create some buzz.
Like what?
Like getting 'secretly' photographed
while shopping together.
A lot of CPs use this trick.
You know a lot about this, huh?
I did some research.
I'm a fast learner.
When are you leaving?
Are you eager for me to leave?
Yeah.
With you here, I can't focus on work.
You seem to be doing just fine to me.
I'm faking it.
If you don't leave soon,
I really won't be able to keep it up.
I like men.
Is your name 'Men'?
I triggered you.
No.
You make me feel completely at peace.
You've never abandoned me.
I'll save this batch of tea for you.
I'll save it till I die.
What on earth does 'no ku-ku-ku'
during the Dragon-Elephant Festival mean?
It's true. All the locals believe it.
So what happens if you break the rule?
You want to break it?
Get lost.
Use that to scoop it up.
That's about enough.
Just use that to store it. Store it.
Come on.
The roasting is done. I'm going
to shower first. I'm dying of heat.
Hey, it's not over yet.
You knead it for me.
You'd do anything for money.
I'm almost as tan as you.
Your face is still okay.
My stylist is coming tomorrow.
You want me to stay away?
I want to introduce you to him.
I'm not the one doing a livestream.
Sister Lan, you should know.
Sister Jialin and Sister Lan are
the ones who launched my career.
They're closer to me than my own mother.
So you want to introduce
me to your parents?
I do.
Bro, Sister Jialin is here.
Sister Jialin.
Shi Yuhao posted it.
He hasn't left Molie yet.
The reservoir.
Right.
This is a good picture.
I'm saving it.
Qinglang, do you have any idea
what the repercussions of this are?
Shi Yuhao wants to
create a CP ship with me.
He posts one blurry photo,
so just let him post it.
Who can tell that's me and Changyang?
It doesn't matter who's in that photo.
That photo points directly at you.
If you publicly announce that you're gay,
your career in the entertainment
industry will be over.
Shi Yuhao is dragging you down with him.
Is it worth it to be destroyed by him?
If it weren't for the random Weibo posts
you've been making these past few days,
this would be easy to clear up.
But now, all the details
have been woven into a web,
and there's no room
left for you to explain.
Then I won't explain.
I'll make it official.
You spent seven years climbing
to the top of the mountain,
just to jump off and kill yourself?
Qinglang, you're a celebrity.
How many endorsement contracts do you have?
You took this job.
You have to see it through.
You can't just walk away
from it whenever you feel like it.
Changyang, come with me.
What's up with you two?
This is grown-up business. Don't ask.
Tell me.
Come on.
Xu Changyang, your brother is Wenshu.
Half-brothers, same father.
You met Qingtian through Wenshu.
Qingtian wanted to come to the mountains.
Wenshu introduced me to him.
And Qinglang?
Qinglang said he wanted to find
a quiet place to stay for a few days.
I told him to come to the mountains.
To come to Molie with Qingtian.
You're very precise with your words.
Airtight.
I have nothing to hide.
So, in just a few days,
Qinglang fell in love with you,
and you fell in love with him.
Yes.
Lies. You know who he is.
How dare you take this step?
With your depth of thought,
this couldn't have
happened in just a few days.
Tell me. How much money do you want?
Or, how much did Shi Yuhao promise you?
Does everything have
to be defined by money?
What in this world
doesn't have a price tag?
Don't talk to me about love.
At your age, you don't understand.
I have to go over the livestream
plan with Qingtian tonight.
I'm staying at his place.
I know.
After the livestream tomorrow,
Sister Lan wants you to
come back to the set with me.
We're about to wrap.
We need you for a cameo anyway.
Qinglang?
That Changyang is impressive.
20 years old, clear logic,
precise expression.
Qinglang wasn't half as sharp at his age.
Is he one of Shi Yuhao's people?
Doesn't seem like it.
But people are hard to read.
I've only met him once.
I can't see through him.
Also,
just now, I told Qinglang to come
back to the set with me tomorrow.
He didn't respond.
If you don't come to Molie,
no one can bring him back.
Let's finish the livestream first.
We can use this charity
event to salvage public opinion.
Sister Lan, the makeup
artists are here for touch-ups.
Let's check your hair.
Don't make the hair too
dramatic. Keep it natural.
Okay.
You and Shi Yuhao never did
anything this ridiculous back then.
Is it that ridiculous?
It's all over the trending topics.
How is that not ridiculous?
Before, you'd run your Weibo
posts by the company first,
or ask for Sister Lan's opinion.
Do you have other plans now?
Or do you want to stay in the
mountains and be a tea farmer?
That's not out of the question.
I've learned how to do it all anyway.
Picking and roasting tea.
If the livestream sales go well,
I'll just sell tea on
livestreams from now on.
Did you eat too many
mushrooms and get poisoned?
Termite mushrooms are poisonous.
Bro, the host will go over
the rundown with you in a bit.
[Qinglang is asking Changyang
to arrange the wrap party dinner]
Hello?
Oh, okay.
Handsome.
What are you doing?
Waiting for your livestream.
I'll give you a secret signal later.
When you see it, post a comment for me.
There are so many people.
Will you be able to find me?
Yes. I'll have Qingtian screen-record it.
I'll look for it after the stream.
Hey, babe.
Hey, get a few more phone numbers later.
And register a few more TikTok accounts.
Then use the name Ji
Zongjun for all of them.
Ji as in 'machine.'
Jun as in 'handsome.'
And the 'Zong' in the
middle is as in 'to track.'
After that, go to Qinglang's livestream.
And post comments in his comment section.
Just pretend to be his fan.
The content should be, uh,
stuff like 'I love you, ' 'I like you.'
'Wow, so handsome.'
Things like that.
Oh, during the livestream,
he's going to make a...
uhh, a hand gesture.
I'll send it to you then.
I'll forward it to you in a bit.
And when he makes that
gesture, you have to post.
Okay?
So I should just keep spamming the
comments with the Ji Zongjun accounts?
Yep. Love you, babe.
Teacher Ye, this is my brother.
Oh, hello.
Hello, Teacher Ye.
That's right.
Let's see, we'll basically...
Teacher Ye.
Yes?
The factory director is looking for you.
Oh, okay, okay.
Excuse me.
Pardon me for a moment.
[Changyang: What does the
gesture you just made mean?]
[Figure it out yourself]
You suck to the core. Am I right?
[I'm right, aren't I?]
[Setting off firecrackers [???]]
Go on, laugh.
Is it too late to back out
of the livestream now?
Too late.
Then you have to
screen-record for me later.
What for?
If you don't, I'm not doing the stream.
Everyone, we have five minutes.
Teacher Ye.
Sorry to interrupt.
Let's continue our run-through.
Okay, everyone, look up and
check the lighting on your faces.
Welcome, everyone, to the
Molie Tea Plantation livestream.
Today, we're very lucky to have invited
a fellow tea lover to our livestream.
Hello, everyone.
I'm happy to meet you all
here on 'A Taste of Time.'
The setting for today's
livestream is so beautiful.
Before we officially begin,
I have to show everyone the
tea mountains in the distance.
I remember you like a
book about tea mountains.
'A Winter Sun Wakes the
Wind in Spring Hills' Dream.'
Yes.
My distant tea mountains,
watching their sea from
thousands of miles away.
The comment section is already flooded.
Wow, so many fans are named Ji Zongjun.
Then let's introduce
today's seven types of tea.
Sounds good.
Then Teacher Ye will have to
tell me the story behind each tea.
Let's start with the simplest one.
Dongguo has a tragic
and beautiful love story.
Legend has it there was a
young couple in the village.
The girl left the village for school.
The boy stayed behind to grow tea.
Their paths diverged from that day on.
They never crossed again.
Later, the boy named
the tea he grew 'Dongguo.'
It means that after
experiencing separation,
and understanding life's many trials,
only then can you know how
precious it is to be together.
Daxue Mountain, as its name suggests,
is pure and clean, without a speck of dust.
It preserves a pristine, primeval forest.
The thousand-year-old Tea
King Tree is in Daxue Mountain.
Molie.
Xigui, Dongguo.
Daxue Mountain.
Yiwu, Nanpo.
Lao Man'e.
Incredible. Teacher Feng,
you know all of them.
I had an expert guiding me.
An expert? What kind of expert?
Hello, Teacher Ye.
Hi, Yuhao. Hello.
Qinglang.
My signal is a bit weak
over here. Hello, everyone.
I'm here now at the
thousand-year-old Tea King Tree.
Let me show you all.
Wow, it's breathtaking.
I feel... I feel that compared to it,
we are all just travellers in time.
What's going on?
Who connected the call?
Tang Chen said she touched it by mistake.
And you believe that?
Check... check her social media accounts.
Who's going to take responsibility
for a livestream accident like this?
I will. It was my negligence.
She must be a fan of Shi Yuhao.
He's like a ghost that won't go away.
And also, Teacher Ye.
Hello.
We need to arrange
tonight's banquet properly.
Okay.
Thank you.
Thanks.
My brother is tired.
I'm very happy.
Let him rest for a bit.
When the tea farmers
saw your livestream data,
they all cried.
I know everyone has worked hard.
You've worked even harder than us.
Ah, thank you, thank you.
It's nothing, it's nothing.
We're leaving now. Let's go.
Take care.
Okay, thank you.
Okay, okay.
We'll be going then. You all get some rest.
Okay, take care.
Okay.
Bye-bye.
See you later. Get some good rest.
Let's all pack up. Everyone, pack up.
Let's go.
Teacher Ye.
Yes?
You knew Shi Yuhao was
going to call in, didn't you?
He came to me this morning
and said you had
arranged for him to call in.
I was vaguely aware of his 'CP'
relationship with Teacher Feng.
The director just wanted to sell more tea.
You should have at
least told us in advance.
You people don't understand
how fandoms work at all.
Where are you?
Still at the venue.
Is there still a celebration
banquet tonight?
Yes.
Enemies on all sides.
And you're laughing?
You backed out of the variety show.
Of course he'd try to
sabotage your livestream.
Just handle things tonight. Wait for me.
Let's see how you're going to get here.
I'll fly over.
Master.
Hey.
Send me the screen recording.
The video file is a bit big.
I'll send it to you from my
cloud drive when I get back.
No, I want to see it now.
Are you okay?
Couldn't be better.
That was a dirty move by Shi Yuhao.
He's got even dirtier tricks up his sleeve.
I noticed the comment
section was full of 'Ji Zongjun.'
He must have arranged it.
Is Shi Yuhao that desperate now?
Why does he have to cling to my brother?
There's a fan on Weibo called Ji Zongjun.
The CP fans all think it's Shi
Yuhao's alternate account.
He hasn't been doing
well since they 'un-coupled.'
You know what a scumbag he is.
He has tons of boyfriends and girlfriends.
If, at that moment, the real
Ji Zongjun had spoken in the comments,
I heard he had a girlfriend
a couple of years ago
who scammed him out of all his money.
The CP fans could have easily
dug up that he wasn't Ji Zongjun.
So he found a bunch of 'Ji Zongjuns'
to stage that kind of situation.
No wonder.
He thinks he's so clever.
I feel like he's not even human anymore.
He's also too clever for his own good.
He's like a husk of a person
with its soul scooped out.
I've said it before.
That movie will be
the peak Shi Yuhao will look
up to for the rest of his life.
He'll never surpass it.
You seem to be enjoying this.
I'm not enjoying it because of him.
Is Qingtian there?
But Qinglang is different.
He'll go much higher
because he knows how to be grateful.
He's talking with Sister Jialin.
Only grateful people can go far.
No need.
Sister Lan has helped my brother a lot.
The livestream mistake...
don't yell at him for it.
Of all the people I know...
Okay.
Sister Lan is the most perceptive.
Master.
Hm?
You and Sister Lan are old friends, right?
Yeah, we've known each other for 15 years.
For a person to stay
the same for 15 years...
that's so difficult.
[What kind of comment did you
leave? None of them seem like you.]
[Take your time to find it.]
No matter her position,
Xing Lan has always stayed true to herself.
The changing times don't sway her.
[He's trying to call
Changyang but can't connect]
It's the Dragon Elephant Festival,
so we can't serve meat.
I've been eating a lot of meat lately.
A vegetarian meal is a nice change.
It's a good thing it's the
Dragon Elephant Festival.
Otherwise, you would've
had to slaughter a pig for us.
That would be too much trouble.
Oh.
No need. Our local
piglets are delicious.
I'll make sure you all get
to try some after the festival.
Please, have a seat.
Even if you take pictures, we
won't allow you to post them.
If you post them without our permission,
we can sue you.
Welcome, welcome.
You took this photo, right?
It's a great shot.
Next time, I can have the
lighting crew set up some lights
so you can get a clearer picture.
But if it were clearer,
you'd be able to see the
person in the photo isn't you.
I've saved the picture.
Thank you.
I like it a lot.
He likes it a lot too.
Come on.
Yuhao.
Aren't you going to
toast Sister Jialin first?
Come on, Sister Jialin.
You're just the same as
you were seven years ago.
Still playing favorites.
Only doing styling for Qinglang.
Now that's not fair.
How was I supposed to know
you'd show up unannounced today?
I'm heading out.
Just say I went to the restroom.
Where did he go?
To the restroom.
So much stuff.
To elope with you.
Aren't you going to ask where we're going?
I'm the one being kidnapped here.
I don't have the right to ask.
If you're tired, you can sleep.
We've still got an hour to go.
When you stand here, don't
all your troubles just melt away?
And the sunrise tomorrow
morning will be spectacular.
This is my secret spot.
I haven't brought anyone else here.
Is there more?
You need a nest egg to elope.
I don't think I loved you
this much in my past life.
Because it wasn't enough,
I have to make it all
up to you in this life.
Ah.
Hey.
No one saw me sneak out, right?
[No one] other than me.
It's cold. Hurry back inside.
Come out and take a picture with me.
If we take one, do you dare post it?
Of course.
I dont' think my brother has a signal.
How's this one?
Post it.
Fine, I'll send it to you.
You're cheating!
Yep.
Well, it's not like I'm scared.
Then what are you scared of?
Losing you.
Just come back for now.
Ask Qingtian for the
details on Xu Changyang.
And get Mr. Xu's contact info.
One, two, three.
Director Du, two more sections
of track won't be enough.